<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The CrossThink</title>
    <description>The CrossThink</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 18:36:43 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 18:36:43 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Naming The CrossThink</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Naming an interdiscplinary student-led Computer Science Journal for the 21st Century is no easy task. You need to maintain delicate balances of wit vs esotericism and clever vs wannabe. We wanted a name that spoke for itself. Yes, it’s ironic that we’re writing an entire post about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computer Science today is a lot more than advancing Moore’s Law. It’s over-encompassing nature naturally spills over to multiple disciplines effortlessly. This also leads to issues in these intersections that have never existed before. Atleast not in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Always eyes watching you and the voice enveloping you. Asleep or awake, indoors or out of doors, in the bath or bed—no escape. Nothing was your own except the few cubic centimeters in your skull.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However fiction doesn’t need to confine itself within the mundane boundaries of reality, does it? Thanks to Orwell’s classic curriculum-staple, dystopian novel 1984, we always had a frame of reference that is unfortunately turning into the present-day reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CrossThink&lt;/strong&gt; is a word in Newspeak, the fictional dialect of Oceania: the totalitarian superstate that is the setting of Orwell’s Nineteen Eighty-Four. It is a noun-verb, and can be used as either, in conventional English. It refers to the cross-pollination of thought that we expect to bring about in our journal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>/naming-crossthink/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/naming-crossthink/</guid>
        
        <category>France</category>
        
        
        <category>Lifestyle</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
